<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" version="2.0" >
    <channel>
        <title>Barcroft TV PressPlay TV MRSS</title>
        <description>PressPlay TV</description>
        <link>http://www.barcroftmedia.com</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2016 05:57:23 GMT</pubDate>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 09:59:53 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 09:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
            <title>Tiny Teen: Primordial Dwarf Teenager Hopes To Be A Star</title>
            <category>Real Life</category>
            <description>TINY teenager Hannah Kritzeck loves singing, ballet and dancing to hip-hop, despite being just 39in tall. The 19-year-old was born with primordial dwarfism, a rare condition that only affects about 100 people in the world, which causes short stature and health problems, including the threat of brain aneurysms and a shortened life-span. Hannah, who wears children's size four shoes, has to bravely face the reality of her condition, while also dealing with
                the normal teenage challenges. A new film follows Hannah as she prepares for graduation from high school, choosing a career, dreaming about boys and finding a date for her end of year prom. The bubbly teen, who weighs just over two stone, also spends her free time taking hip-hop and ballet classes and has her own voice coach.  Hannah was adopted by Jackie and Larry Kritzeck at birth and grew up in Minnesota, USA, but she soon learned her normal teenage
                experiences were going to be different from those of her friends. Her condition comes with many medical needs including annual MRI scans to check for the possibility of brain aneurysms and because her teeth and mouth are so small she has dental implants. She also developed scoliosis and had two titanium rods placed in her back when she was young. But despite the limitations posed by her condition, Hannah has never let it get in the way of her passion for dancing.
                * Little and Looking for Love is on Wednesday February 11, 9pm, on TLC</description>
            <author>Barcroft</author>
            <media:title>Tiny Teen: Primordial Dwarf Teenager Hopes To Be A Star</media:title>
            <media:keywords>Amazing People</media:keywords>
            <media:credit>Barcroft Media</media:credit>
            <media:copyright>© Barcroft Media</media:copyright>
            <media:description>TINY teenager Hannah Kritzeck loves singing, ballet and dancing to hip-hop, despite being just 39in tall. The 19-year-old was born with primordial dwarfism, a rare condition that only affects about 100 people in the world, which causes short stature and health problems, including the threat of brain aneurysms and a shortened life-span. Hannah, who wears children's size four shoes, has to bravely face the reality of her condition,
                while also dealing with the normal teenage challenges. A new film follows Hannah as she prepares for graduation from high school, choosing a career, dreaming about boys and finding a date for her end of year prom. The bubbly teen, who weighs just over two stone, also spends her free time taking hip-hop and ballet classes and has her own voice coach.  Hannah was adopted by Jackie and Larry Kritzeck at birth and grew up in Minnesota, USA, but she soon
                learned her normal teenage experiences were going to be different from those of her friends. Her condition comes with many medical needs including annual MRI scans to check for the possibility of brain aneurysms and because her teeth and mouth are so small she has dental implants. She also developed scoliosis and had two titanium rods placed in her back when she was young. But despite the limitations posed by her condition, Hannah has never let it get in
                the way of her passion for dancing. * Little and Looking for Love is on Wednesday February 11, 9pm, on TLC</media:description>
            <media:category label="Real Life">Real Life</media:category>
            <media:content medium="Video" duration="284" expression="full" fileSize="478399123" height="1080" width="1920" type="video/quicktime" lang="en" url="http://barcroftmrss.mainstreamdata.com/mrss/assetstore/BDV1086/BDV1086/HR_MOV/BDV1086.mov" />
            <media:thumbnail url="http://barcroftmrss.mainstreamdata.com/mrss/assetstore/BDV1086/BDV1086/JPG/BDV1086.jpg" height="720" width="1280" />
            <guid isPermaLink="false">BDV1086</guid>
            </item><item>
            <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 09:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
            <title>41lbs And Still Growing: Meet The Giant 10 Month Old Baby</title>
            <category>Real Life</category>
            <description>A 10-MONTH-OLD baby in India has weighed in at an astonishing 18.7kg (2st 13lbs) - the weight of an average six-year-old girl. Aliya Saleem, whose parents live in a remote village in the Indian state of Jharkhand, was born at a relatively large 4kg (9lbs), but started rapidly piling on the pounds once she hit the four month mark. Her enormous weight has put her life in danger and placed a huge strain on the already limited
                finances of her parents, dad Mohammad Saleem and mum Shabana Parveen, who are struggling to cover the costs of her daily food intake and the regular need for new clothes. The family has until now been unable to afford to take her to a hospital, but were able to get a consultation at Fortis Hospital to see a specialist in a bid to get to the bottom of Aliya's condition.</description>
            <author>Barcroft</author>
            <media:title>41lbs And Still Growing: Meet The Giant 10 Month Old Baby</media:title>
            <media:keywords>Amazing People</media:keywords>
            <media:credit>Barcroft Media</media:credit>
            <media:copyright>© Barcroft Media</media:copyright>
            <media:description>A 10-MONTH-OLD baby in India has weighed in at an astonishing 18.7kg (2st 13lbs) - the weight of an average six-year-old girl. Aliya Saleem, whose parents live in a remote village in the Indian state of Jharkhand, was born at a relatively large 4kg (9lbs), but started rapidly piling on the pounds once she hit the four month mark. Her enormous weight has put her life in danger and placed a huge strain on the
                already limited finances of her parents, dad Mohammad Saleem and mum Shabana Parveen, who are struggling to cover the costs of her daily food intake and the regular need for new clothes. The family has until now been unable to afford to take her to a hospital, but were able to get a consultation at Fortis Hospital to see a specialist in a bid to get to the bottom of Aliya's condition.</media:description>
            <media:category label="Real Life">Real Life</media:category>
            <media:content medium="Video" duration="243" expression="full" fileSize="307775442" height="1080" width="1920" type="video/mp4" lang="en" url="http://barcroftmrss.mainstreamdata.com/mrss/assetstore/BDV2093/BDV2093/HR_MPG/BDV2093.mp4" />
            <media:thumbnail url="http://barcroftmrss.mainstreamdata.com/mrss/assetstore/BDV2093/BDV2093/JPG/BDV2093.jpg" height="720" width="1280" />
            <guid isPermaLink="false">BDV2093</guid>
            </item><item>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <title>Inventor Builds Steampunk Inspired Automatron Car</title>
            <category>Cars</category>
            <description>ECCENTRIC British inventor Paul Bacon has gone 'full steam ahead' on his latest customised car. Dubbed the “Automatron”, Paul’s latest steampunk-style creation is his most expensive build to date and is still not completed. Looking like something out of Chitty Chitty Bang Bang, the Automatron boasts a supercharged V8 engine and uses a switch gear from a Lancaster Bomber to start. The front wheels are
                from an Austin 7 and he has used the biggest street legal tyres for the rear wheels.

                Videographer / director: Jack Stevens
                Producer: Tom Gillespie, Nick Johnson
                Editor: Jack Stevens</description>
            <author>Barcroft</author>
            <media:title>Inventor Builds Steampunk Inspired Automatron Car</media:title>
            <media:keywords>car,cars,Barcroft Cars,Barcroft Media,BDV2841,Barcroft TV,retro,retro car,futuristic,inventor<Plug>PeepOpenetrohead,hobby,invent,engine,speed,top speed,fast,machine,incredible,amazing,news,footage,video,tinker,car parts,steampunk</media:keywords>
                <media:credit>Barcroft Media</media:credit>
                <media:copyright>© Barcroft Media</media:copyright>
                <media:description>ECCENTRIC British inventor Paul Bacon has gone 'full steam ahead' on his latest customised car. Dubbed the “Automatron”, Paul’s latest steampunk-style creation is his most expensive build to date and is still not completed. Looking like something out of Chitty Chitty Bang Bang, the Automatron boasts a
                    supercharged V8 engine and uses a switch gear from a Lancaster Bomber to start. The front wheels are from an Austin 7 and he has used the biggest street legal tyres for the rear wheels.

                    Videographer / director: Jack Stevens
                    Producer: Tom Gillespie, Nick Johnson
                    Editor: Jack Stevens</media:description>
                <media:category label="Cars">Cars</media:category>
                <media:content medium="Video" duration="293" expression="full" fileSize="590366180" height="1080" width="1920" type="video/mp4" lang="en"
                    url="http://barcroftmrss.mainstreamdata.com/mrss/assetstore/BDV2841/oIeMGlPBKTfi/HR_MPG/BDV2841-Automatron---Online-Use_PUP.mp4" />
                <media:content medium="Video" duration="293" expression="sample" fileSize="158062724" height="960" width="1280" type="video/mp4" lang="en"
                    url="http://barcroftmrss.mainstreamdata.com/mrss/assetstore/BDV2841/oIeMGlPBKTfi/1280_H264_MP4/BDV2841-Automatron---Online-Use_PUP.1280.mp4" />
                <media:content medium="Video" duration="293" expression="sample" fileSize="78729865" height="640" width="854" type="video/mp4" lang="en"
                    url="http://barcroftmrss.mainstreamdata.com/mrss/assetstore/BDV2841/oIeMGlPBKTfi/854_H264_MP4/BDV2841-Automatron---Online-Use_PUP.854.mp4" />
                <media:content medium="Video" duration="293" expression="sample" fileSize="50206170" height="480" width="640" type="video/mp4" lang="en"
                    url="http://barcroftmrss.mainstreamdata.com/mrss/assetstore/BDV2841/oIeMGlPBKTfi/640_H264_MP4/BDV2841-Automatron---Online-Use_PUP.640.mp4" />
                <media:thumbnail url="http://barcroftmrss.mainstreamdata.com/mrss/assetstore/BDV2841/oIeMGlPBKTfi/JPG/NCU_automatron_0292_bs_0000000006670030_BO8.jpg" height="720" width="1280" />
                <media:thumbnail url="http://barcroftmrss.mainstreamdata.com/mrss/assetstore/BDV2841/oIeMGlPBKTfi/JPG-1280/NCU_automatron_0292_bs_0000000006670030_BO81280.jpg" height="720" width="1280" />
                <media:thumbnail url="http://barcroftmrss.mainstreamdata.com/mrss/assetstore/BDV2841/oIeMGlPBKTfi/JPG-640/NCU_automatron_0292_bs_0000000006670030_BO8640.jpg" height="360" width="640" />
                <media:thumbnail url="http://barcroftmrss.mainstreamdata.com/mrss/assetstore/BDV2841/oIeMGlPBKTfi/JPG-228/NCU_automatron_0292_bs_0000000006670030_BO8228.jpg" height="128" width="228" />
                <media:thumbnail url="http://barcroftmrss.mainstreamdata.com/mrss/assetstore/BDV2841/oIeMGlPBKTfi/JPG-74/NCU_automatron_0292_bs_0000000006670030_BO874.jpg" height="42" width="74" />
                <guid isPermaLink="false">BDV2841</guid>
                </item><item>
                <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 09:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
                <title>Surfer's Paradise! 30 Mile Waves Hit River In Indonesia</title>
                <category>Adventure</category>
                <description>IT'S a surfers paradise, the wave that can last for up to 30 miles. The Bono tidal bore - which surges down the river Kampar in a remote region of Indonesia - has become legendary in surfing circles. The
                    challenging wave is said to travel around 10mph, but has been known to roll up to 30 miles upriver before breaking - helping some surfers ride waves for an hour straight. It means surfers have begun flocking to the area
                    around full and new moons to make the most of the phenomenon. But the wave - created by a strong tide pushing up the river, against the current - isn't for the feint hearted. Crocodiles, pythons and boa constrictors are
                    said to inhabit the river basin. But despite the potential dangers, unfazed riders packed a stretch of the Kampar river during November's Bono Bekudo cultural festival.</description>
                <author>Barcroft</author>
                <media:title>Surfer's Paradise! 30 Mile Waves Hit River In Indonesia</media:title>
                <media:credit>Barcroft Media</media:credit>
                <media:copyright>© Barcroft Media</media:copyright>
                <media:description>IT'S a surfers paradise, the wave that can last for up to 30 miles. The Bono tidal bore - which surges down the river Kampar in a remote region of Indonesia - has become legendary in surfing
                    circles. The challenging wave is said to travel around 10mph, but has been known to roll up to 30 miles upriver before breaking - helping some surfers ride waves for an hour straight. It means surfers have begun
                    flocking to the area around full and new moons to make the most of the phenomenon. But the wave - created by a strong tide pushing up the river, against the current - isn't for the feint hearted. Crocodiles,
                    pythons and boa constrictors are said to inhabit the river basin. But despite the potential dangers, unfazed riders packed a stretch of the Kampar river during November's Bono Bekudo cultural
                    festival.</media:description>
                <media:category label="Adventure">Adventure</media:category>
                <media:content medium="Video" duration="54" expression="full" fileSize="78607588" height="1080" width="1920" type="video/quicktime" lang="en"
                    url="http://barcroftmrss.mainstreamdata.com/mrss/assetstore/BDV1191/BDV1191/HR_MOV/BDV1191.mov" />
                <media:thumbnail url="http://barcroftmrss.mainstreamdata.com/mrss/assetstore/BDV1191/BDV1191/JPG/BDV1191.jpg" height="721" width="1280" />
                <guid isPermaLink="false">BDV1191</guid>
                </item><item>
                <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 09:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
                <title>TIGER SWIM: Bengam Tiger Dives For Food</title>
                <category>Animals</category>
                <description>Odin, the white Bengal Tiger, in his enclosure in San Francisco. British keeper Lee Munro has been training Odin, who is the top new attraction at Six Flags Discovery Kingdom in San
                    Francisco, since he was just 6. The park is one of the only places in the world where people can see a tiger diving for food.</description>
                <author>Barcroft</author>
                <media:title>TIGER SWIM: Bengam Tiger Dives For Food</media:title>
                <media:keywords>Wildlife &amp; Natural World</media:keywords>
                <media:credit>Barcroft Media</media:credit>
                <media:copyright>© Barcroft Media</media:copyright>
                <media:description>Odin, the white Bengal Tiger, in his enclosure in San Francisco. British keeper Lee Munro has been training Odin, who is the top new attraction at Six Flags Discovery
                    Kingdom in San Francisco, since he was just 6. The park is one of the only places in the world where people can see a tiger diving for food.</media:description>
                <media:category label="Animals">Animals</media:category>
                <media:content medium="Video" duration="103" expression="full" fileSize="160176568" height="720" width="1280" type="video/mp4" lang="en"
                    url="http://barcroftmrss.mainstreamdata.com/mrss/assetstore/BDV042/BDV042/HR_MPG/BDV042.mp4" />
                <media:thumbnail url="http://barcroftmrss.mainstreamdata.com/mrss/assetstore/BDV042/BDV042/JPG/BDV042.jpg" height="720" width="1280" />
                <guid isPermaLink="false">BDV042</guid>
                </item><item>
                <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2016 09:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
                <title>Cute Pet Pig In New York City</title>
                <category>Animals</category>
                <description>Adorable two-and-a-half-year-old pig Wilbur hams it up for the cameras as he walks down New York City streets with owner Nadine Darsanlal. Emotional support
                    animal, Wilbur, accompanies Nadine, a disabled Navy veteran, everywhere she goes, providing therapeutic benefits through companionship and affection. Wilbur, a
                    Juliana and Pot-Bellied Pig mix, even sleeps in Nadine's bed at night and lets her brush his teeth in the morning.</description>
                <author>Barcroft</author>
                <media:title>Cute Pet Pig In New York City</media:title>
                <media:keywords>Animals</media:keywords>
                <media:credit>Barcroft Media</media:credit>
                <media:copyright>© Barcroft Media</media:copyright>
                <media:description>Adorable two-and-a-half-year-old pig Wilbur hams it up for the cameras as he walks down New York City streets with owner Nadine Darsanlal.
                    Emotional support animal, Wilbur, accompanies Nadine, a disabled Navy veteran, everywhere she goes, providing therapeutic benefits through companionship and
                    affection. Wilbur, a Juliana and Pot-Bellied Pig mix, even sleeps in Nadine's bed at night and lets her brush his teeth in the morning.</media:description>
                <media:category label="Animals">Animals</media:category>
                <media:content medium="Video" duration="119" expression="full" fileSize="319183886" height="720" width="1280" type="video/quicktime" lang="en"
                    url="http://barcroftmrss.mainstreamdata.com/mrss/assetstore/BDV1057/BDV1057/HR_MOV/BDV1057.mov" />
                <media:thumbnail url="http://barcroftmrss.mainstreamdata.com/mrss/assetstore/BDV1057/BDV1057/JPG/BDV1057.jpg" height="720" width="1280" />
                <guid isPermaLink="false">BDV1057</guid>
                </item><item>
                <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2016 09:59:53 GMT</pubDate>
                <title>Thunder Dome: Storm Chaser Captures Supercell Timelapse</title>
                <category>Planet</category>
                <description>An incredible storm spreads across the sky and reaches down into the earth in a devastating display of nature's power. Shot on
                    June 4 by extreme weather enthusiast Robert Sinner, 34, this timelapse shows a ferocious supercell move across the countryside in Hanston,
                    Kansas.</description>
                <author>Barcroft</author>
                <media:title>Thunder Dome: Storm Chaser Captures Supercell Timelapse</media:title>
                <media:keywords>Wildlife &amp; Natural World</media:keywords>
                <media:credit>Barcroft Media</media:credit>
                <media:copyright>© Barcroft Media</media:copyright>
                <media:description>An incredible storm spreads across the sky and reaches down into the earth in a devastating display of nature's
                    power. Shot on June 4 by extreme weather enthusiast Robert Sinner, 34, this timelapse shows a ferocious supercell move across
                    the countryside in Hanston, Kansas.</media:description>
                <media:category label="Planet">Planet</media:category>
                <media:content medium="Video" duration="64" expression="full" fileSize="103763974" height="1080" width="1920"
                    type="video/mp4" lang="en"
                    url="http://barcroftmrss.mainstreamdata.com/mrss/assetstore/BDV2303/BDV2303/HR_MPG/BDV2303.mp4" />
                <media:thumbnail url="http://barcroftmrss.mainstreamdata.com/mrss/assetstore/BDV2303/BDV2303/JPG/BDV2303.jpg"
                    height="720" width="1280" />
                <guid isPermaLink="false">BDV2303</guid>
            </item>
        </channel>
    </rss>
